好了 这是他的尿布袋
Okay, here's his diaper bag.
这是他的温奇先生
And his Mr. Winky.
还有
And...
噢
Oh!
他 嗨
Him. Hi!
一切都还好吧
So how did everything go?
很好 有一次喷射性的呕吐事件
Oh, great. Great. There was a projectile throwing up incident.
但是他先开始的
But he started it.
我们要走了      好的
We've gotta go.         Okay.
噢 对了
Oh, right.
我有个消息要宣布 是关于我们的
I've got some news. It's about us.
你和我吗      不 苏珊和我
Oh, you and me?         Uh, no. Susan and me.
另一个我们
The other "us".
好吧
Okay.
我们
We're...
我们要结婚了
We're getting married.
就像 "现在宣布你们成为妻子和妻子" 那种结婚吗
As in "now pronounce you wife and wife" married?
我们希望你能参加
Anyway, we'd like you to come.
如果你不想来 我们也完全能够理解
But we totally understand if you don't want to.
当然 我为什么会不想去呢
Yeah, well, why wouldn't I want to come?
第一次婚礼我很开心
I had fun at the first wedding.
我只是想说
Look I just thought that...
不 不 不 我为什么不能替你们高兴呢
No no no, I mean, hey, why shouldn't I be happy for you.
我怎么会 不为你们的喜悦而狂欢呢
You know, I mean, what would it say about me if I couldn't revel in your joy?
我会狂欢的 相信我
And I'm reveling, baby. Believe me.
你的手指被椅子夹住了吗
Is your finger caught in that chair?
嗯哼
Hmm
要我们走吗      嗯哈
Want us to go?         Uhhuh.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第02季 第11集
同志婚礼  The One With the Lesbian Wedding
调校制作：海盗美剧 寒 枫
字幕编辑：海盗美剧 小龟快快跑
你好像有烦恼
You're clearly bothered by something.
告诉我是什么
Why don't you tell me what it's.
太酷了 你真的要上电视了
This is so cool. You're actually gonna be on television.
我知道 我昨晚才真的感觉到
I know. It really hit me last night.
我要参加"我们的日子"的演出
I'm gonna be on "Days of our Lives".
然后我开始想我们的事
Then I started thinking about all of us.
这还真是属于我们的日子
And how these are the days of our lives.
好耶      什么
Yes!         What?
帮卡萝儿和苏珊办婚宴的人 骑山地车出意外了
Carol and Susan's caterer had a mountain bike accident this weekend.
全身都打了石膏
And she's in a fullbody cast.
好耶
Yes!
她们要我帮忙 太酷了 我从来没办过婚宴
They want me to do it, which is really cool since I've never catered before.
并且我真的需要钱 这对你不构成问题吧
And I really need the money. And this isn't a problem for you, is it?
这重要吗      真是太好了
Would it matter?         Oh, you are so great!
谢谢
Thank you!
你真的不去吗      我真的不去
You're really not going?        I'm really not going.
我搞不懂
I mean, I don't get it.
她们已经同居了 为什么还要结婚呢
They already live together. Why do they need to get married?
因为她们彼此相爱
Because they love each other.
而且 她们想跟亲朋好友一起分享那份爱
And they wanna celebrate that love with the people that are close with them.
你要硬这样讲就算
If you wanna call that a reason.
谁是客厅里最苦情的男人
Who's the bitterest man in the living room?
客厅里最苦情的男人
The bitterest man in the living room?
你好 邻居
Hi, neighbor!
罗斯 我以为你已经不在乎了
Ross, I thought you were over this.
跟这个没有关系好吧 她是我的前妻
Look, that has nothing to do with this, okay? She's my ex-wife.
如果她和一个男人结婚
If she were marrying a guy,
你们谁都不会觉得我应该去
none of you'd expect me to be there.
如果她嫁给一个男人
Hey, if she were marrying a guy,
那她就是史上最烂的女同志了
she'd be like the worst lesbian ever.
我错过了吗
Did I miss it?
没有 这个家伙自杀后就换我了
No, I'm on right after this guy shoots himself.
哇 她很漂亮
Whoa, she's pretty.
是呀 而且她人也很好
Yeah. Oh, and she's really nice too.
她教我怎么样在镜头前演戏
She taught me all about, you know, how to work with the cameras
还有闻屁演戏法
and smell the fart acting.
抱歉 你说啥     你说什么
I'm sorry, what?         Excuse me?
要在这么短的时间内 记住这么多台词
It's like, you got so many lines to learn so fast that
有时候需要一点时间想下一句
sometimes you need a minute to remember your next one.
所以 当你想的时候呢
So while you're thinking of it,
你停顿一下 要看起来很专注
you take this big pause where you look all intense.
就像这样
You know, like this...
了解
Oh. Okay.
到我了 我出来了
Oh, here's my scene! Here's my scene!
华莱士太太      是的
Mrs. Wallace?         Yes.
我是德瑞克雷莫瑞医生 令妹的神经外科医生
I'm Dr. Drake Ramoray, your sister's neurosurgeon.
她会没事吧
Tell me, is she gonna be all right?
恐怕 情况比我们预计的还要糟
I'm afraid the situation is much more dire than we'd expected.
令妹罹患了
Your sister's suffering from a
颅下血肿
subcranial hematoma.
或许 我们可以边喝咖啡边聊
Perhaps we can discuss this further over coffee.
很不错
Nice!
刚有那么一会儿 我还以为 你真的在闻什么东西呢
For a minute, I thought you were actually trying to smell something.
再来一次
Do it again!
太棒了       再来一次
That was so good!        One more time.
好吧 好吧
All right, all right.
可恶 毕佛曼 就在病历上
"Damn it, Braverman! It's right there on the chart!"
太精彩了 好了 我要去上班了
That's great. All right, I gotta get to work.
我还有一个大的恐龙骨头要检查
I got a big dinosaur bone to inspect.
不 那是我
No no no, that's me.
对喔
Oh, right.
噢      噢
Oh!        Oh!
谢谢 我没办法
Oh, thanks. Couldn't...
你还好吧
Is everything okay?
不好
No.
今天我有一个客人 死在按摩床上
One of my clients died on the massage table today.
我的天啊
Oh my God.
你也让他们太放松了吧
That's a little more relaxed than you want them to get.
是啊
Yeah.
她已经82岁了
She was, you know, 82 years old.
她叫艾道曼太太
And her name was Mrs. Adelman.
亲爱的
Oh, honey.
感觉好奇怪
Yeah, it's just so strange.
她早上醒来时 说不定在想
I mean, y'know, she probably woke up this morning and thought,
我先吃点早餐 再去散会儿步
All right, I'll have some breakfast. And I'll take a little walk.
然后去按摩一下
And, and you know, then I'll have my massage.
但是她不知道上帝想说 "好的 但是到此为止"
Little did she know God was thinking "Okay, but that's it".
但是最诡异的一件事就是
Oh, but the weirdest thing was
她死的时候 我正在帮她清理灵气
okay, I was cleansing her aura when it happened.
当她的灵魂离开身体后
And when her spirit left her body,
我认为它没有走远
I don't think it went very far.
这是什么意思
What do you mean?
我想它上了我的身
I think it went into me.
天哪 真的好难
God, this is so hard.
我没法决定要选羔羊肉还是鸭肉
I can't decide between lamb or duck.
当然 羊羔比较恐怖
Well, of course, lambs are scarier.
要不然那部电影 就会叫做"沉默的鸭子"
Otherwise the movie would've been called "Silence of the Ducks".
好了 谁点了什么
Okay, who ordered what?
我相信我点了 喝了一半
Oh, I believe I had the half-drunk
杯缘还有口红印的卡布奇诺
cappuccino with the lipstick on the rim.
这杯里面有烟屁股的 是无咖啡因的吗
Yes, and this with the cigarette butt in it, is that decaf?
我的天啊
Oh God.
我真不相信你妈过来 你会这么紧张
I can't believe you're so uptight about your mom coming.
我知道 但是这是她第一次来 我只是不想让她认为
I know, but it's just it's the first time. And I just don't want her to think that
因为我没嫁给巴瑞 我的生活就完全是垃圾
because I didn't marry Barry that my life is total crap, you know?
说到垃圾 你该听听史黛拉尼德曼
Talk about crap, try listening to Stella Neidman
讲她跟施洛德的 老掉牙的故事
tell her story about Rod Steiger for the hundredth time.
菲比 你觉得这位女士 会跟我们在一起多久
Pheebs? How long do you think this lady will be with us?
不知道 很显然她还有未完成的心愿
I don't know. She obviously has some kind of unfinished business.
坐直
Sit up!
乖女儿
There she is.
妈      甜心
Mom!        Hey, sweetie!
这就是你工作的地方
So this is where you work!
真是太棒了
Oh, it's wonderful!
这是客厅还是餐厅 谁分得出来呢
Is it a living room? Is it a restaurant? Who can tell?
我想这就是乐趣所在吧
I guess that's the fun.
差不多 来 看看我的朋友们
Pretty much. Here, meet my friends.
摩妮卡 你看起来真美
Monica! You look gorgeous!
天啊 我上次看到你 你还在拼了命地吃
Oh, my! The last time I saw you, it was eat or be eaten.
这位是乔伊
This is Joey.
这位是菲比
This is Phoebe.
这位是钱德
And this is Chandler.
你记得罗斯吧
And you remember Ross?
你好 罗斯      你好 葛林太太
Oh, hello, Ross.         Hi, Mrs. Green.
那么
So,
你们觉得我女儿如何
what do you think of my daughter
穿着围裙 有份大事业
in the apron with the big job!
妈
Oh, Mom!
没有你来倒咖啡 大家都休想喝到东西
If you didn't pour the coffee, no one would have anything to drink.
相信我 有时真的会这样
Believe me, sometimes that happens.
这真的太让人兴奋了 我从来都没工作过
This is just so exciting! You know, I never worked.
我从我父亲的家直接
I went straight from my father's house
到女生联谊会宿舍 然后到我丈夫家
to the sorority house to my husband's house.
我真是以你为傲
I am just so proud of you!
真的吗      真的
Oh, Really?        Yes.
我知道你让我想起了谁
I know who it is you remind me of.
艾芙林邓末
Evelyn Durmer.
当然是在她做拉皮手术失败之前
Of course that's before the lousy facelift.
现在她长得像苏比赛尔斯
Now she looks like Soupy Sales.
菲比 艾芙林邓末是谁
Pheebs? Who's Evelyn Durmer?
我不知道 谁是苏比赛尔斯
I dont know. Who's Soupy Sales?
我的天
Oh my God!
那边有一个丑男人 光着身子在拉大提琴
There's an unattractive nude man playing the cello.
是啊 还好他不是在演奏一个比较小的乐器
Yeah, well just be glad he's not playing a smaller instrument.
你的确有了自己的生活 甜心
You have some life here, sweetie!
我知道 妈 我知道你和爸爸都很生气
I know. And Mom, I realize you and Dad were upset
我没嫁给巴瑞
when I didn't marry Barry
住在郊区的大房子里
and get the house in the suburbs
过着又安全又衣食无忧的生活
with all the security and everything.
但是现在对我来说更好 你知道吗
But, God, this is just so much better for me, you know?
我知道 你根本不爱巴瑞 亲爱的
I do know. You didn't love Barry, honey.
我从来没看到过 你这么开心
And I've never seen you this happy.
我看着你 然后想 这就是我想要的
I look at you and I think, "Oh, this is what I want."
是说我吧
For me.
不只是你
Well, not just for you.
什么意思
Well, what do you mean?
我正考虑离开你爸爸
I'm considering leaving your father.
好了 告诉我这是不是太赞了
All right, tell me if this is too cute.
女同志婚礼 鸡胸肉
Lesbian wedding, chicken breasts.
天啊 我想我快吐了
Oh God! I think I'm gonna be sick.
怎么了 我又没在上面加乳头
What? It's not like I'm putting little nipples on them.
你不知道他们感情不好吗
And you had no idea they weren't getting along?
完全不知
None.
他们不常吵架吗
They didn't fight a lot?
才不会 他们根本不说话
No, they didn't even talk to each other.
天啊 我怎么会知道 他们之间有问题啊
God, how was I supposed to know they were having problems.
在我的年代 是不能离婚的
You know, in my day, divorce was not an option.
看是谁来了
Hey, look who's up!
我真不敢相信会发生这种事
Oh, I just can't believe this is happening.
我小时候 每个人的父母都在离婚
I mean, when I was little, everybody's parents were getting divorced, y'know?
我想我已经长大了 就不用担心这个问题了
I just figured as a grownup, I wouldn't have to worry about this.
你可以把这件事当做是种赞美吗
Well, is there any chance that you can look at this as flattering?
她这么做是想变得更像你
I mean, she's doing it because she wants to be more like you.
那她学我的发型不就行了
Well, then, you know, couldn't she have just copied my haircut?
好玩的是 我父母离婚时 他们带我去看心理医生
You know, it's funny when my parents got divorced, they sent me to a shrink.
她跟我说 所有的孩子都会责怪自己
And she told me that all kids have a tendency to blame themselves.
就你而言 这真应该怪你呢
But in your case it's actually kinda true.
他来了
Oh,that's him.
可恶 我邮购订的爷爷还没寄到
Damn. My mailorder grandfather hasn't come yet.
菲比      是的 你好 艾道曼先生
Phoebe?         Yes. Hi, Mr. Adelman.
很高兴见到你      谢谢你过来
Nice to see you.         Hi, thanks for meeting me.
没关系 但你的确打扰了我 忙碌的呆坐一天
Oh, that's all right, although you did cut into my busy day of sitting.
要不要坐下
Do you wanna sit?
不用了 我花了大半个上午才站起来
Oh, no, no, please, I spent most of mid-morning trying to stand up.
我能为你做些什么 亲爱的
What can I do for you, my dear?
好吧 我不知道该怎么说
Oh, okay, I don't know how to say this, but,
我认为 当你太太的灵魂脱离身体时
I think when your wife's spirit left her body,
她转移在了 我的身体里
it kind of stuck around in me.
你是说 我老婆附在你身上
You're saying my wife is in you?
对 你不用相信我
Yeah. Okay. You don't have to believe me.
但是 你知道她有什么没完成的愿望吗
But can you think of any unfinished business she might have had?
她逗留人间的原因
Like any reason she'd be hanging around?
我不知道该怎么说 亲爱的
Well, I don't know what to tell you dear.
我唯一想到的就是
The only thing I can think of is that
她常说 在死之前 她想要看遍世上的一切
she always used to say that before she died, she wanted to see everything.
一切      一切
Everything?         Everything.
那是很多事情耶
Whoa. That's a lot of stuff.
等等
Oh, wait, I...
我记得她也说过 她想跟我上最后一次床
I remember she also said she wanted to sleep with me one last time.
对不起 我脑袋里出现了笑声
I'm sorry. There's laughing in my head.
值得一试 对吧
Worth a shot. huh?
看看这个
Look at this.
这些是三年前的万圣节
These are all Halloween three years ago.
你看 这是巴瑞
Oh, and look, here's Barry.
他直接从诊所过来吗
Did he have to come straight from the office?
不 那是他的变装服
Oh. no. That was his costume.
他其实是牙齿矫正医生 但是他装扮成一般的牙医
See he's actually an orthodontist, but he came as a regular dentist.
两位      啥事
You guys?        Yeah.
记得我之前说 谢谢 我不需要你们帮忙
Remember when I said before, "thank you, but I don't really need your help"?
事实上 你说的是
Actually, what I think you said was
别碰那个 滚出我的厨房
"Don't touch that and get the hell out of my kitchen."
真的吗 真奇怪 不管怎样
Really? Weird. Anyway...
我本来计划得很好
See,I planned everything really well.
我计划 计划再计划
I planned and I planned and I planned.
结果是 我没有计划好足够的烹饪时间
It just turns out, I don't think I planned enough time to actually do it.
嘿 摩妮卡 你需要帮忙吗      你想帮的话
Hey, Mon, you want some help?         If you want.
大家好      你好
Hey.         Hey.
好累的一天
What a day.
我带她到处跑
Oh, I took her everywhere.
现代艺术博物馆 洛克斐勒中心
The Museum of Modern Art, Rockefeller Center,
自由女神像
the Statue of Liberty.
她还跟着你吗
She's still with you?
对啊 我想她还没看完吧
Yes. I guess she hasn't seen everything yet.
我马上回来 她又要去洗手间了
I'll be right back. She has to go to the bathroom again.
这脸蛋真漂亮
Such a pretty face!
真的好好玩喔 只有女生
Oh, this is so much fun. Just the girls.
你知道我们该做什么吗
Do you know what we should do?
你们有大麻吗
Does anybody have any marijuana?
天啊
God!
听着 不准在这些食物旁抽大麻
All right, look, no one's smoking pot around all this food.
那就算了
Well, that's fine.
我从来没抽过 我只是想试试看
I never did it. I just thought I might.
那么
So,
有没有新的性爱招式
what's new in sex?
What's new in sex?
我只跟你爸在一起过
The only man I've been with is your father.
我在切 我在切 什么都没听到
I'm dicing. I'm dicing. I don't hear anything.
这不是不尊重你爸
I mean, this is no offense to your dad, sweetie.
但是我在想
But I was thinking,
可能有更精彩的
there might be more.
抱歉 你知道吗 我没有办法跟你谈这个话题
Oh, I'm sorry. You know what? I cannot have this conversation with you.
好啦 好啦 好啦
All right. All right.  All right.
老天 你还没告诉爸爸 就先跟我丢这个炸弹
I mean, god, you just come in here and drop this bomb on me before you even tell Daddy.
怎么样 你到底要怎么样 想要得到我的祝福吗
What? What do you want? Do you want my blessing?
不是
No.
那你要我说服你别这样吗      不是
You want me to talk you out of it?        No.
那你到底想怎样
Then what? What do you want?
我只是以为所有的人中 只有你会理解
I guess, I just figured of all people, you would understand.
为什么我会理解
Why on earth would I understand this?
你没嫁给你的巴瑞 亲爱的
You didn't marry your Barry, honey.
但是我嫁了我的
But I married mine.
噢
Oh!
各位 我们有麻烦了
All right people, we're in trouble here.
我们只剩下12小时36分钟了
We've only got 12 hours and 36 minutes left.
快 快 快
Move, move, move!
摩妮卡 我觉得你应该配上德语字幕
Monica, I feel like you should have German subtitles.
乔伊 加快速度
Joey, speed it up!
对不起 都是猪的错 它们不想被卷进去
I'm sorry! It's the pig. They're reluctant to get in the blanket!
摩妮卡 怎么会这样 我以为你都计划好了
Monica, how did this happen? I thought you had this all planned out.
你想让我哭吗
Do you want me to cry?
你就是想要我哭 对吗
Is that what you want?
你想看我哭吗
Do you wanna see me cry?
不想 长官
Sir, no, sir!
好了 你
All right, you!
不 我跟你说过 我不参与这件事
What? No. Look, I told you I am not a part of this thing.
好吧 罗斯 我知道你跟卡萝儿和苏珊 之间有心结
All right, look, Ross. I realize that you have issues with Carol and Susan.
我很同情你 真的
And I feel for you, I do.
但如果你不帮忙 我会用一堆热狗
But if you don't help me cook, I'm gonna take a bunch of those little hot dogs
创作一道新开胃菜 叫做"罗斯猪肉卷"
and create a new appetizer called "Pigs In Ross".
好 挖香瓜球
All right, ball a melon!
喂 为什么我得切丁 而他只要挖香瓜球
Hey! How come I'm stuck dicing, when he gets to ball the melon?
嗨      进行得怎么样
Hi!        Hi, how's it going?
很好 照进度进行得很好
It's going great! Right on schedule.
我有一群快乐的小帮手
Got my little happy helpers.
很好 随便啦
That's fine. Whatever.
怎么了
What's the matter?
没事
Nothing.
好吧 有事 我想我们要取消婚礼了
Okay, everything. I think we're calling off the wedding.
什么
What?
你还是会付我钱的 对吧
You're still gonna pay me, right?
或者不这么自私
Or something a little less selfish.
卡萝儿 怎么了 发生什么事了
Carol, what's the matter? What happened?
我父母今天下午打电话来说 他们不来
My parents called this afternoon to say they weren't coming.
天啊
Oh my God!
我知道他们不能接受这件事
I mean, I knew they were having trouble with this whole thing.
但他们是我父母
But they're my parents.
他们应该在婚礼上把我交出去
I mean, they're supposed to give me away and everything.
我很遗憾
Okay, I'm sorry.
因为我说应该取消婚礼
And then Susan and I got in this big fight
苏珊和我大吵了一架
because I said maybe we should call off the wedding.
她说 这不是为了他们 是为了我们
And she said "we weren't doing it for them, we were doing it for us".
如果我不了解这个的话 或许就真的应该取消婚礼
And if I couldn't see that, then maybe we should call off the wedding.
我不知道该怎么做
I don't know what to do.
我不敢相信我会这么说 但是苏珊说的对
I can't believe I'm gonna say this, but I think Susan's right.
真的
You do?
你爱她吗 你不需要太强调这件事
Look, do you love her? And you don't have to be too emphatic about this.
我当然爱她
Of course I do.
那就是了
Well then, that's it.
如果乔治和艾德莱不能接受 那就别管他们
And if George and Adelaide can't accept that, then the hell with them.
如果我父母不希望我娶你
Look, I mean, if my parents didn't want me to marry you,
他们也无法阻止我
no way that would've stopped me.
这是你的婚礼
But this is your wedding.
就结吧
Do it.
你说得对 你当然是对的
You're right. Of course you're right.
那我们继续
So we're back on?
我们继续吧
We're back on.
你们听到她说的 剥 切
You heard the woman! Peel! Chop! Devil!
真不敢相信 我损失了两分钟
Can’t believe I lost two minutes.
看起来 毫无意义
It just seems so futile.
虽然有这么多女人 但是跟没有一样
You know? All these women, and nothing!
我觉得就好像 失去了神力的超人
I feel like Superman without my powers, you know?
我有披风 却不能飞
I have the cape, and yet I cannot fly.
现在你知道 我每天都是什么感觉了吧
Well, now you understand how I feel every single day.
这个世界就是我的女同志婚礼
Okay? The world is my lesbian wedding.
要奶油糖吗
Butterscotch?
没人要吗
No one?
好吧 你们等下会后悔的
All right, you'll be sorry later.
谢谢你      不客气
Thank you.         Anytime.
罗斯
Ross.
没有任何一件事比
You know, nothing makes God happier
两个人能够彼此因爱而结合 更能让神感到快乐
than when two people, any two people, come together in love.
亲朋好友 我们今天齐聚一堂
Friends, family, we're gathered here today
参加卡萝儿和苏珊神圣的婚礼
to join Carol and Susan in holy matrimony.
我的天
Oh my God!
现在我什么都看过了
Now I've seen everything!
她走了 她走了 她走了
Whoa, she's gone. She's gone. She's gone.
继续结婚吧 继续 继续
Go ahead, get married. Go, go!
你看看她们
Would you look at them?
对 忍不住不看
Yeah. Can't help but.
觉得这个热狗卷不错吧
How's that pig in the blanket working out for you?
那是我卷的喔
I wrapped those bad boys.
我好想萝丝      是吗
I miss Rose.         Oh, yeah?
我知道有点奇怪 但是
I know it's kind of weird, but I mean,
她曾经是我生命很重要的一部分
she was a big part of my life there, you know.
不知道 我只是觉得有点孤单
And I don't know. I just feel kind of alone.
我刚不小心听到你说的话
You know, I couldn't help overhearing what you just said.
我想你应该忘记萝丝 继续你的人生
And I think it's time you forget about Rose, move on with your life.
我们去拿杯酒好吗
How about we get you a drink?
好啊 你真好
Okay. So nice!
我连想句搭讪的话都不用 对吗
I shouldn't even bother coming up with a line, right?
妈 开心吗
Hey, Mom, you having fun?
我刚跟一个很棒的魁梧女人跳舞
Oh am I! Ijust danced with a wonderfully large woman.
还有三个女生 在自助餐吧对我暗送秋波
And three other girls made eyes at me over at the buffet.
我不是说 这是我想追求的东西
Oh, I'm not saying it's something I wanna pursue.
但是很高兴知道 我还有别的选择
But it's nice to know I have options.
还有酒 对吧
There's more alcohol, right?
你好吗
How you doing?
很好
Okay.
你今天做了好事      对
You did a good thing today.        Yeah.
想跳舞吗
You wanna dance?
不用 没关系
No, that's fine.
来吧
Come on.
我让你带舞
I'll let you lead.
好吧
Okay.
听着 有没有鸟不重要
All right look, penis schmenis!
好吗 我们都是人
Okay? We're all people.
我们之中谁会最先结婚
Okay, which one of us do you think is gonna be the first one to get married?
摩妮卡 我结过婚了
Mon, I was married.
我也是 技术上来说      我办过婚礼
Yeah, me too, technically.         I had a wedding.
好吧 我只是想找个有趣的话题聊天
All right, just trying to start an interesting discussion.
我有一个 我们之中谁会最晚结婚
All right, I got one. Which one of us do you think will be the last to get married?
小本也算吧
Isn't Ben in this?
当然      绝对的
Of course!         Absolutely.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧